本字幕由高清电台整理发布，更多高清电影请访问
https://gaoqing.fm
我的名字叫Dave Robicheaux
My name's Dave Robicheaux.
我是个酒鬼
I'm an alcoholic.
有时，我受到酒精的诱惑
Sometimes I'm tempted to have a drink.
但我不能这样做
But I never do.
我希望这个可怜的女孩死以后
I hope this poor girl was dead
他才开始像这样切开她
before he started carving on her like that.
Dave，这个女孩没有这么好运气
This poor girl didn't have
a whole lot of good luck, Dave.
在古代
In the ancient world,
人们把沉重的石头，垒在他们死后的坟墓上
people placed heavy stones on the graves of their dead
这样他们的灵魂就不会迷路，受到生活的折磨
so their souls would not wander
and afflict the living.
我总觉得这是原始人
I always thought this was simply the practice
单纯的迷信行为
of superstitious and primitive people.
但是，我学会了关于死亡
But I was about to learn that the dead
死亡带着稠密和发光的迷雾
can hover on the edge of our vision
环绕在我的眼前
with the density and luminosity of mist.
他们要求合理的安息于地下
And their claim on the earth can be as legitimate
向我们自己一样顽强的
and tenacious as our own.
我能看一下你的驾驶执照吗？
Could I see your driver's license, please?
我的什么？
My what?
驾驶执照
Driver's license.
请从你的钱包里把它取出来，拿给我
Please take it out your billfold,hand it to me.
哦，好吧，行
Oh, yeah, sure.
Well...
我刚才不太小心
I was a little careless back there.
对此我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
你是Elrod T,sykes?
You're Elrod T. Sykes?
是的，长官，我正是
Yes, sir,that's who I am.
下车，Sykes先生
Step out the car,Mr. Sykes.
好吧，长官，你什么意思，长官
Yes, sir.Anything you say, sir.
Sykes先生，我想你喝酒了
Mr. Sykes,I think you've been drinking,
而且还在你的车里吸食大麻
and I know you've been smoking
marijuana in your automobile.
我相信你的女朋友在吃螳螂
I believe your lady friend there
just ate the roach.
哦，好吧，那现在情况不太妙是吗？
Ooh, well, that wouldn't be good now, would it?
你现在因饮酒驾车被捕了，先生
You're under arrest for driving while intoxicated, Mr. es.
我会带你到离开这条街，到市立监狱
I'll take you just down the street here to the city jail.
我会派一部车，把送Drummond小姐回去
I'll send a car, take Ms.Drummond wherever she's staying.
但是你的红色小跑车
But your little red sports car
会被拖到拘留所
is going to be towed to the pound.
是个坏消息
This is bad news.
这不在我的议程里
This is not on my agenda,
因为我们刚开始一部新电影
'cause we're just starting a movie.
我一直喜欢你的所以电影
I've always enjoyed all your films.
Drummond小姐也是
Ms. Drummond's too.
请把你的车钥匙拔下来
Take your car keys out the ignition please.
El,干点什么
El, do something.
我觉得真是糟透了
I feel real bad about this.
能让他给母亲反酒后驾驶活动
Can he make a contribution
进行捐款，或其他类似的事吗？
to Mothers Against Drunk Driving or something like that?
就像你个你的崇拜者，Drummond小姐
As an admirer of your work,Ms. Drummond,
我提醒你，别再提捐款的事
I recommend you don't make any more mentions of contributions.
我劝你原地不动
I recommend you stay put.
你就独自在这儿，几分钟后带你回家
Deputy will be along here in a few minutes to take you home.
Allons.
在我的车上，你不会晕车吧？
You're not going to get sick in my truck, are you?
不，
No, I'm just fine.
我知道那儿有一具死尸
I know where there's a dead body.
什么？
What?
看上去像一大堆软骨和骨头
Looks like a big pile of gristle and bone.
这是那儿？
Where was this?
走出他妈的Atchafalaya沼泽
Way the hell out in Atchafalaya swamp.
我们必须找出靠近印第安人保留地的一个地方
We had to pick up a scene near the old Indian reservation.
我过去撒尿
I went to take a leak.
我看见他陷在一个沙州里面
I saw it sticking out of a sandbar.
回车上去
Get back in the truck.
这个沼泽里都是老印第安人的尸体
That swamp full of old Indian bones.
但是
Yeah, but...
对不起，我不记得你的名字了
Sorry, I didn't catch your name.
Dave Robicheaux.
Robicheaux先生
当我找到那个印第安人
now, if that was an Indian I found,
我真是奇怪为什么
I was wondering what he was doing
他被链子绑住
with a chain wrapped around him.
再说一遍
Say that again.
一条生了锈的大铁链
It's a rusted chain with links
好像他的拳头
as big as my fist
交叉在他的胸口
crisscrossed around his rib cage.
你还能再找的那个沙洲吗？
Can you find that sandbar again?
是的，长官，我相信我能行
Yes, sir,I believe I could.
我会给你一个改过自新的机会
I'm going to make a confession to you,
Sykes先生.
看见那些是很痛苦的事
DWIs are a pain in the butt.
要是我放你回家，你告诉你
If I take you home, can I have your word
明天早上9点到我办公室来
you'll be in my office,9:00 in the morning?
镇定点？
And sober?
9点钟过去，当然
9:00, you got it.Absolutely.
哦，我真的感谢你
Hey, I really appreciate this.
Elrod Sykes和Kelly Drummond?
我也要去
I want to go to the set.
Sykes是个醉鬼
Sykes is a drunk.
他很棒
He's huge!
他的脑袋在黑暗里发光
His head glows in the dark.
也许我们能得到一个他的海报亲笔签名
Maybe we could get an autographed movie poster.
没门
No way!
不是为你，是狂风慈善基金
Not for you,for the hurricane relief fund.
好的，太棒了
Okay, cool.
求你了
Please?
别闹了
Will you hush?
我带着她
I'll take her
照顾她
and look out for her,
要是你没意见
if that's all right with you.
也许我们还能得到Kelly Drummond的签名
Maybe we could get Kelly Drummond to sign one too,
为某人的房顶
pay for somebody's roof.
求你了
Please?
还在那边
It's over yonder.
等一下 ，Sykes先生
Hold on there,Mr. Sykes.
最好用点这些东西
Best put some of this on.
我们曾经在带来很多装备到这里
We used to have a lot of bats down here,
蚊子还是咬所有人
but the mosquitoes ate 'em all.
这家伙从好莱坞过来可是走了很长的路
That boy's a long way from his Hollywood poontang,
是吗
ain't he?
这傻瓜说的是帮你
This jackass is objectifying you,
Sykes先生，因为他有点暴露狂
Mr. Sykes, because he's had very little exposure
在外边的环境下
to the outside world.
别让他烦你
Don't let it bother you.
也许65年伊丽莎白飓风吹过这里，也许把他埋了
Hurricane Betsy blowing through here in '65 probably buried him
卡特李娜飓风又把他挖出来
and Katrina unearthed him.
为什么是65年？
Why '65?
飓风从古至今一直在这个国家横行霸道
Hurricanes tear up this part of the country all the time.
看见这些筋骨了吗？
See that left shin bone?
剩下一半了
Clipped in half.
在那儿，当他像跑时，他们射了他
That's where they shot him when he tried to run away.
你是个心理学家，或者在这里胡说？
You a psychlc or some bullshlt like that?
不，我在一英里见过这场景
No, I saw it happen about a mile from here.
你是那是些白人吗？
Are you saying that some whlte people
这周围人们用私刑吗？
lynched somebody around here?
我们回去后，你必须去和你们上级谈谈
When we get back, you're going to have to talk to your sheriff,
让这个验尸官现在离开这里
get the coroner out here now.
我不懂为啥你们都在Iberia教区
I don't know about y'all over in Iberia Parish,
但是这周围，在之前的40年来
but around here,ain't nobody going to be
没有人真正的去关心黑鬼们的苦难
real interested in nigger trouble that's 40 years old.
Robicheaux先生，你在找什么？
What are you looking for,Mr. Robicheaux?
我没看到在他裤子上那些剩余的带子
I don't see any remnants of a belt on his trousers...
或者靴子上的绳子
or any laces in his boots.
这家伙购物的时候是大概很善意的
That boy probably did his shopping at the Goodwill.
他们从未找到他，甚至没去找过
They never found him,didn't even look for him.
回来后，没有尸体，没有失踪人口报告
Back then, with no body,no missing persons report,
局长没有任何理由去相信我
that sheriff didn't have any reason to believe me,
起码有一小块屁股，去证明
must less get off his ass and go to work.
你不再是十七岁了
You're not 17 years old anymore.
这个麻烦已经影响到了你的工作之外的生活
The trouble I have with you is getting you away from work.
你做了你能做得一切
You've done everything that you can.
没有任何理由再去自责
You have no good reason to beat yourself up.
快喝了你的牛奶，上床睡觉吧
Now drink your milk and come to bed.
我陪你去
I'm horny.
Bootsie是对的
Bootsie was right.
在过去的岁月，什么才是影响的重点呢？
What was the point of reaching into the distant past?
就在昨天，一个年轻女孩被分尸
Just yesterday, a young girl had been eviscerated.
我们查到她的名字叫Cherry LeBlanc
We had her name now,Cherry LeBlanc.
Trajan先生在吗？
Mr. Trajan around?
他在那边，Chere
He's over there, chere.
我们已经被查了三次了
We've been over this already three times now.
Cherry几星期之前就不在这里干了
Cherry's been working here off and on for the past few weeks.
她表现出来很听Hogman Pitan的话
She's going to show up anyway to listen to Hogman Pitan.
这个女孩为Hagman做的一件事
The girl had a real thing for Hogman.
大概是一点，她把她的钱包放在酒吧
Some time around 1:00,she put her purse behind the bar
说她向到外面去散散步
and says she's going to go outside for a walk.
你知道她因为卖淫被逮捕了吗？
You know she'd been arrested for prostitution?
我不知道那件事
I didn't know that.
好吧
All right.
好的
Okay.
你雇用了她，因为你认为
You hired her 'cause you thought
她是个LSU 好学生
she was an honor student at LSU.
我并没有留意，你告诉我的这事，侦探先生
I can't say I care for the way you're talking to me, Detective.
要是我发现你隐瞒了什么
If I found out you've been holding back information on me,
Trajan先生，我下次会带上搜查令来，Trajan先生
Mr. Trajan, I'ma come back here with a warrant, Mr. Trajan,
逮捕你
for your arrest.
你知道Cherry LeBlanc
Did you know Cherry LeBlanc,
白人小妞，大概十九岁
little white girl,about 19 years old?
她在这里工作？
She work here,ain't she?
你知道他有个男友，叫Tante的吗？
Do you know if she had a boyfriend, tante?
要是你想打听什么
If that's what you want to call it.
她在卖淫
She in the business.
Trajan先生有关系吗？
Was Mr. Trajan involved?
去问他吧
Ask him.
我觉得他没干
I don't think he was.
除此之外，你还有东西告诉我
Otherwise you wouldn't be　telling me all these things.
她是个可怜的女孩
She a sad girl.
我告诉她，“像你这样漂亮的白人女孩
I told her,"A pretty white girl like you
能做你想做的任何事”
could have anything you want."
这个姑娘打扮起来，就像个电影明星
When that girl dress up,she look just like a movie star.
谁给她拉皮条？
Who was her pimp?
我不再知道其他的事了，我
I don't know nothing else, me.
她被一些有钱的白人
She wasn't about to give the name
和一个黑人老妇叫去
of some rich white man to an old black woman.
什么有钱的白人？
What rich white man?
一些有钱的白人也许 。。
Some rich white man maybe...
让她别再卖淫，去卖果冻
get her out of the business
of selling jelly roll.
她说不久前有人打了他们
She say that just before somebody done them
给这个年轻姑娘带来可怕的事
awful things to that young girl.
局长也在ST,Clair教区
The sheriff over in St. Clair Parish
说“很感谢”“感谢这些警察昨天在Atchafalaya
said, "Thanks a lot,"for that pile of bones you found
找到这些骸骨
out in the Atchafalaya yesterday.
他们真的赏识这些额外的工作
They really appreciate the extra work.
他需要去找到一条新的工作线索
He need to find a new line of work,
他不喜欢他们那些骨头
he don't like them bones.
现在，他会说，欢迎你取消你的日常工作
Now, he said you're welcome to come over on your days off
全力进行调查
and run an investigation.
那些验尸官拿走了骨头，现在正等你呢
Their coroner's got them bones now waiting on you.
解剖的结果证明是LeBlanc女孩
Autopsy report came in on that LeBlanc girl.
看上去我们在谈论一个神经病患者
Looks like we're talking about a psychopath,
有人用金属丝连上了眼睛，还弄破了
somebody wired to the eyes on crack or meth.
也许
Maybe.
我想她认识凶手
I think she knew him.
但你别以为“那是John(俚语不懂)”？
So you don't think it was a John?
不，她把钱包留在了吧台
No, she left her purse behind the bar
她所有的避孕套都在里面
with all her condoms in it.
Cherry LeBlanc是一个有野心的职业女性(讽刺)
Cherry LeBlanc was a working girl with ambition.
也许他在那儿丢了一个商业机会（讽刺）
Maybe she misjudged a business opportunity here.
那些女孩会去干卖淫的勾当呢？
Who's a girl like that going to be in business with?
Um... Baby Feet?
也许是Baby Feet
Maybe Baby Feet.
发生了什么,Cholo?
What's happening, Cholo?
我以为你在写作呢
I thought you was in the pen.
不，伙计
No, man.
Katrina,她把我的手洗干净
Katrina,she rinsed my hands clean.
所有的他妈的晦气的东西
The whole damn crlme lab
都洗到河里去了
washed off down the river.
我在新奥尔良可没犯什么事
Ain't got nothing on me in New Orleans.
干得好，兄弟
Doing fine, bro.
除了这个，他们没有支付足够的钱
Besides that, they ain't even got enough money
给手下的兄弟，至少想我
to lobotomize guys like me no more.
有何贵干，Dave?
What's going on, Dave?
我正在调查一件谋杀案，Julie
I'm investigating a murder,Julie.
真是不幸
No kldding.
你们都担心我，Dave?
Y'all worried about me,Dave?
哦，是的
Hell yes.
哪有人会承认是他们自己
How many guys would burn down their own
老爸夜总会和它的老爸一直都在这里
father's nightclub with their own father still in it?
要是我搞点小坏事，看在我态度好的情况下
You got to forgive me if I get a little upset
你该原谅我，Dave
by these kinds of attitudes, Dave.
我回家里拉屎
I come home to this shithole.
我保证我们都是正规的娱乐生意
I'm a prominent man in the entertainment business.
我每天都在打电话，你能在加利福尼亚的
I talk on the phone every day to people in California
每周娱乐杂志上读到这些
you read about in Entertainment Weekly.
他们也许会说“欢迎回到Balboni日”
They ought to have "Welcome Back Balboni Day."
相反
Instead,
我却被你像管道煤气一样对待（说他危险）
I get treated like sewer gas by you.
你明白我说的意思吗，Dave
You understand what I'm saying, Dave.
伤了我的心
It hurts me.
坐下摆摆龙门阵
Sit down while I take a whiz.
Cholo.你的好客精神哪去了？
Cholo,where's your hospitality?
给这哥们一杯软饮料
Get the man a soft drink.
这儿，陆军中尉
Here, Lieutenant.
Julie告诉我，那时候
Julie was telling me about that time
法兰西38区几乎四分之一的黑鬼
that nigger almost popped you with a .38
都被你抓了
in the French Quarter.
说他救你的命
Said he saved your life.
你和Julie是高中棒球队的成员吗？
Weren't you and Julie baseball buddies in high school?
我发现，Cholo
Take the hint,Cholo.
这家伙不善言谈
This guy's not a conversationalist.
你调查过Cherry的LeBlanc交易吗？
You working on that Cherry LeBlanc deal?
你还知道些什么？
What you know about that?
今天全打开了，伙计们
All over today's paper, man.
Julie和我刚好谈到这些
Julie and me were just talking about it.
好像你在让一个呕吐的病人放松
Sounds like you got one sick fuck on the loose.
我很忙，Julie
My meter's running,Julie.
我想谈谈，我们在南面
I want to talk about
发现了那个被害的女孩
that murdered girl we found south of town.
哪个女孩？
Which girl is that?
Cherry LeBlanc.
我猜想我没听过这个名字
I guess I ain't heard about it.
你不看报纸吗？
You don't read the newspaper?
我很忙
I've been busy.
我能看见
I can see that.
我们以前是朋友，Dave
We used to be friends,Dave.
我甚至可能给过你很多支持
I even maybe did you a favor once.
所以我要同你和你的管片保持联络
So I'm going to line it out for you and any locals
想变成你们的眼线
that want to get the wax out their ears.
路易斯安那屁股被打了
Louisiana's flat-ass broke.
新奥尔良是个停尸房
New Orleans is a mortuary.
从厕所的下面到
And the bottom of a toilet's got more appeal
河口的屁眼里面
than this shithole in the bayou.
所以事实上，他们最好醒目点
So they better wake up to the fact
我投下了超不多400万美金
that we are dropping close to $40 million
在Iberia教区
in Iberia Parish.
他们不喜欢想像
They don't like the name
Balboni这样的名字在这儿？
Balboni around here?
我就把整个他妈的电影业
We'll move the whole fucking movie
搬到密西西比去
over to Mississippi.
看看那些熊屁股的
See how that floats with those coon-ass jack-offs
商会会怎么样
on the Chamber of Commerce.
你现在有电影生意？
You're in the movie business now?
是的，我拍摄Whlte Doves和Michael Goldman
Yeah, I'm producing Whlte Doves with Michael Goldman.
你怎么会想知道这事？
What you think about that?
我想大家都希望你成功，Julie
I'm sure everybody wishes you success, Julie.
我下一部是关于棒球的电影
I'ma do a baseball movie next.
你想在里面演一个角色吗？
You want a part in it?
你能走了
You can go on in.
还记得我吗，Dave?
You remember me, Dave?
是Doucet
It's Doucet, isn't it?
是的，长官，Murphy Doucet
Yes, sir,Murphy Doucet.
你记性真好
You got a good memory.
我在Jefferson教区的治安部门
I was with the Jefferson Parish Sheriff's Department
那时你还在NOPD
when you were with NOPD.
我猜你现在电影公司
I guess you're in the movie business now,
没和其他人在一起
along with everybody else.
是的，我在安全服务部门兼职
Yeah, I own half of a security service now,
我还在干货车驾驶员
and I'm still with the Teamsters out of Lafayette.
我在这儿是身兼两职
So I'm kind of doing double duty here.
遇到什么麻烦了吗？
Is there some kind of trouble?
我在哪儿能找到Goldman先生？
Where can I find Mr. Goldman?
他们正好在这片树林的另一边
Right on the other side of them trees.
我来告诉他，你来了
I'll let him know you're coming.
好的，我要找到他
It's all right.I'll find him.
我们把士兵分成两队，列队通过那儿？
We had two divisions of soldiers march through that?
看上去我们要求袭击面包房
Looks like we're shooting a bread commercial.
在哪儿布置大炮，美国玩具R?
Where'd we get this cannon,Toys "R" Us?
是的，我需要平民站在那边
All right, I'm going to need floaters in there,
一个脸朝下，两个肚子上
one face down,two belly-up.
用点肥油
Use some of the fat extras.
让他们看上去浮肿
They'll look bloated.
我的死亡之屋？
My dead horse?
不
No.
不在来电表里？太恐怖了
Not on the call sheet?Terrific.
我们需要一些鲜血，鲜血近投地上
We need some blood,blood-soaked ground,
剧本上是这样写的吗
if that's what it says in the script.
这不是每夜新闻
This is not the nightly news.
他们永远渲染血腥
They never show the blood.
这是一个寓言
This is an allegory.
我们不能射下Vicksbury
We're not shooting the fall of Vicksburg.
这是 Baghdad 2007
This is Baghdad 2007.
复制到这些
Copy that.
要是人们不能联络到这些，操他们
If people don't connect the dots, fuck 'em.
有个Robicheaux侦探在这儿要见你，先生
There's a Detective Robicheaux here to see you, sir.
因为你调查一庄罪案
So you're investigating a crime.
看看这周围都是罪犯？
Seen any crime around here?
唯一的罪犯我知道，是我们拖车里的空气条件
Only crime I'm aware of is
the air conditioning in my trailer.
在哪儿你能在坐便器上炸鸡蛋
You could fry an egg on the toilet seat in there.
然后我要带领演员们在沙洲上挖掘骨架
Then I've got a lead actor digging up skeletons
的确我需要去想想
in sandbars, exactly what I need to be thinking about
同时拍一张照片
while I'm shooting a picture.
Goldman先生，这电影是Julus Balboni投资拍摄的吗？
Mr. Goldman, is Mr. Julius Balboni producing this film?
拍摄？
Producing?
我必须要操一下我的前任代理人
I must've really fucked up in my previous incarnation.
也许我陷进了Tltanlc
Maybe I sunk the Tltanlc
或者是被Archduke Ferdinand谋杀了
or assassinated Archduke Ferdinand.
我是唯一的制片人
I am the only producer.
所以Balboni先生撒谎
So Mr. Balboni's lying.
Balboni投资了一些钱到动作电影
Mr. Balboni is investing some of his money in a motion picture.
那样犯法吗？
Is that illegal?
祝贺你
Congratulations.
你和这个人的生意会让你们发家致富的
You in business with the man that hung Fulvio Raneri's cousin
比山西煤老板还有钱
up by his colon on a meat hook.
你认识这个女孩吗？
Do you recognize this girl,
Cherry LeBlanc?
怎么样，Hogman?
How you are, Hogman?
到走廊上来
Come on up on the porch.
座到椅子上
Grab a chair.
你知道那个LeBlanc女孩吗？
You knew that LeBlanc girl,didn't you?
我不喜欢管白人兄弟么的事情
I don't like to have nothing
to do with white folks' business,
但是那些人对那个女孩做的事令我很烦
but it bothers me what somebody do to that girl.
在她离开之前，我和她交谈了大约两小时
I spoke to her about two hours before she left the juke.
她说"Hogman
She said, "Hogman,
在下辈子，我们再结婚吧”
in the next life, me and you going to get married."
这是她说的
That's what she said.
我说“亲爱的，被让人误会你改邪归正，不做鸡了”
I said, "Darling, don't let the men misuse you for no chicken."
她说“我要在Pontchartrain湖边拥有
She said, "I'm going to have myself a town house
一套城里的房子
on Lake Pontchartrain."
她从新奥尔良就和人胡搞吗？
Was she mixed up with somebody from New Orleans?
也许那些白人流氓皮条客告诉她，她很特别
Probably some white-trash pimp told her she special,
她很漂亮
she pretty.
相反，她被自己害死了
Instead,she got herself killed.
你被他们在Atchafalaya找到的骨架
You're mixed up with that skeleton they found
搞糊涂了，是吗？
in the Atchafalaya,ain't you?
你怎么会知道这些？
How do you know about that?
当有人发现一个黑人尸体的时候
When somebody find a dead black man,
黑人们都知道
black people knows about it.
我听说的
I'm listening.
一个蓝鸟不能待在潮鸟的窝里
A blue jay don't sit on a mockingbird's nest.
潮鸟会一直朝蓝鸟不断的大叫
The mockingbird will whoop the blue jay's ass every time.
Sam,我们的在这儿谈什么？
What are we talking about here,Sam?
我想说说一个黑人
I'm talking about a black man.
他和一个白种女人举止失常
And he was carrying on with a white woman
他为那女人的丈夫工作
who husband he worked for.
我想他们就是，你们在沙州挖到的骨架
I think them was his bones you dug in that sandbar.
他叫什么名字？
What was his name?
谁在乎他们的名字？
Who care what's his name?
我想他得到了，他想要的
I think he got what he asked for.
我说，“过去就是过去
I say, "Past is past,
不会被遗忘的”
and don't be messing with it."
你在警告我？
You warning me?
那个白种女人叫什么？
What was that white woman's name?
现在我要去照看我的豆子了
I got to go start my beans now.
Alafair,
你把这个小棕熊放在我的煎饼派上了
you got to keep this raccoon out of my fried pie.
下一次他要是再进来，我就要用我的扫帚打他了
Next time he come in here,I'm gonna swat him with my broom.
Tripod 只是个动物
Tripod's just an animal.
你为什么不把这个臭烘烘的家伙踢出院子？
Why don't you try kicking the smell of cigars out of the yard?
Alafair,你不应该和Batist这样说话
Alafair, you shouldn't talk to Batist like that.
他用暴力的手段恐吓Tripod
But he threatened Tripod with menacing violence.
Tripod是个小浣熊宝宝
Tripod's a raccoon, baby.
快向Batist道歉
Apologize to Batist.
我对刚才的话道歉
Sorry for what I said.
不过这是被Dave逼的
And I'm saying it'cause Dave made me.
真是个漂亮的孩子，Dave
That's a beautiful child,Dave.
顺便告诉你，要是她十八岁了
By the time she's 18 years old,
你的头发会全变白
your hair's going to be solid white,
而且头发会掉的像葛优一样
if there's any of it left.
真是太好了
This is great!
我喜欢这儿
I love it.
你也开着一个小店
You run a bait shop too.
干得怎么样了，Robicheaux先生？
How you doing,Mr. Robicheaux?
今晚我们想请你们，大家去吃晚饭
We want to have dinner with y'all tonight.
谢谢，不过我婆姨已经做好晚饭了
Oh, thanks, but my wife's already cooking supper.
我去参加一个秀场，正好路过这里
I was just on my way over there to take a shower.
哦，快赶路
Well, hurry up.
我们在大娘水饺订了位置，大家都来
We got reservations at Clementine's, everybody.
我们全家今天晚上有活动，Sykes先生
The family has plans for this evening, Mr. Sykes.
真是令人难堪，El
This is embarrassing, El.
我订了位置
I have a reservation.
我不想去，因为有很多麻烦事
Hey, I don't want　to cause any problems.
我们干脆在你的商店里，把酒拿出来
We'll just pick up　our liquids at your store here
不醉不归，怎么样？
and hit the road, okay?
Sykes先生...
你曾经酒后驾驶
you've been driving drunk,
你到一个警官家里，去买很多酒
and you come to a cop's house to buy more booze.
为什么你不让Drummond小姐来开车
Why don't you hand those keys to Ms. Drummond
在你醉倒在路上之前？
before you hit the road?
啤酒在哪儿？
Where's that beer at?
Hey.
你是个好同志
You're a good man.
你们真的要小心点
Y'all need to be real careful.
Elrod是个傻鸟，但我爱他
Elrod's a shitbird,but I love him.
很好
It's all right.
不凑巧，记着下次
Bad timing.Put it there.
好的，下次
Cool.Next time.
Hey.
好的
All right.
哦，该死，我们要给钱
Um, shit.We'll settle up.
我们下次再给钱，好吧？
We'll settle up later,yeah?
好的
All right.
去那边
Other side.
过来
Come here.
好了，过来
Come on.Come here.
Elrod.
什么？看清楚
What?Check this out.
你要停下吗？
Will you stop?
El!
看看我
Check me out.
怎么样？我自己搞的
S'more?Made 'em myself.
哦，谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
Elrod Sykes穿着Dave的运动衫
Elrod Sykes is wearing Dave's jersey.
你相信吗？
Can you believe it?
快去做功课
Now go do your homework.
喝点什么？
Something to drink?
青岛啤酒怎么样？
How about a beer?
我想我们没有
I think we're out.
我确定哪儿还有一瓶
I'm sure there's one in there somewhere.
我要去喂Alafair的兔子了
I'm going to go feed Alafair's rabbits.
你想一起来吗？
You care to join me?
好，好，我去
Yeah, yeah, sure.
过来这儿，Leroy
Get back there, Leroy.
来吧
Go on.
你晚上能在柏树林里看到光亮吗？
You ever seen lights in the cypress trees at night?
那是沼泽的沼气
That's swamp gas.
他们能被点燃，到处飘荡，像球状闪电
It'll ignite and roll out across
the waters like ball lightning.
不，长官，不是这些
No, sir,that's not what it is.
看见那些人在湖的远处出来
See these guys out yonder by the lake.
他们提着灯笼，从一些救护车里出来
They have lanterns hanging from some of their ambulances.
很多士兵的伤口上张满了蛆
A lot of those soldiers had maggots in their wounds.
这就是他们活着的原因
That's the only reason they lived.
用那些蛆来治理传染病
It's 'cause the maggots ate out the infection.
你好像已经醉了很长时间了，Elrod
You've been drunk a long time, Elrod.
等一会儿，所有的树和鳄鱼都会和你说话
Pretty soon all the trees and alligators will be talking to you.
有一次一朵野兰花对我唱了一首歌
A wild orchid sang a song to me one time.
她发出美妙的声音
She had the prettiest voice.
是的，我没醉
Yeah, I wasn't drunk.
这个家伙，一个将军
This guy, a general,
他拄着一根拐杖在水里
he's standing on a crutch right by the water.
他和我说话
And he said to me,
你和你的法律界朋友必须击败他们
"You and your friend the law man must repel them."
我看你在胡言乱语
I think you're delusional.
你可能想去参加一个AA制的聚会
You might want to think about
going to an AA meeting
还带着我一起
with me one time.
可能我喝了一点
Maybe I was a little drunk.
这家伙的鼻子怎么了？
What happened to this dude's nose?
浣熊咬的
Coon bit him.
Lou Girard总是在晚上打电话找我
Lou Girard always called at night.
我曾经在新奥尔良查尔斯湖的水沟里面
I had picked him out of gutters
把他捞起来
from New Orleansto Lake Charles,
在他绝境中救他一命
held him when he had the shakes,
带他回到正常的生活中来
driven him to AA meetings moretimes than I could remember.
同时，他也知恩图报
And he had done the same for me.
谢谢你打电话给我， Lou
Thanks for the call, Lou.
我看见那些电子磁带
Yeah, when I saw that electrical tape
缠绕在她的手、脚，或者其他身体部分
around her hands and her feet,or what's left of them,
我想到你，你正在调查LeBlanc的案子
I thought about you and that LeBlanc case you got going.
现在她在哪儿？
Where she at now?
她还在哪儿，还在桶里
She's right there,still in that barrel.
大约15个蓝螃蟹在她上面
She got about 15 big blue crabs on her.
验尸官说，我们移动她，会让她变成碎片
Coroner says, we move her,she's coming out in pieces.
我们将给个粗略的时间给她一个编号，也许
We're going to have a rough time getting an ID, maybe.
也许根据她的牙齿
Maybe by her teeth.
那个家伙找到她
That's the poor bastard who found her.
你什么时间发现这个桶的？
When did you first notice that barrel?
大概在3～4个星期前
About four or three weeks back.
在哪儿看到什么其他人了吗？
See anyone else out there on that levee?
有啊，大概在一个月前的一个早上
Yeah, about a month ago in the evening,
我看到一辆黑色的车
I seen a dark-colored car.
我记得很清楚，它是崭新的，你知道
I remember thinking,it was brand-new, you know?
没人愿意把他们的新车开道
Why would anybody want to bring their new car
这个满地污泥和坑坑洼洼的路上来
down on that dirt road full of holes?
你记得是什么牌子的车吗？
You remember what kind of car it was?
不，长官，对不起
No, sir.I'm sorry.
我只是希望，不是我唯一找到这个可怜的女孩
I just wish I hadn't been the one to find that poor woman.
我一直没能看看桶里面
And, hey, I'm never going to look inside
的另一个桶
another barrel again.
不，我，不
Not me, no.
你做得很好，谢谢你
That'll do.Thank you.
政府会发给你奖状
Officer Guidry going to take you home.
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要一辆拖车来拖走一样加长豪华车
I need a tow truck to haul off a limousine.
什么位置？
Where about?
别让他跑了
Can't miss it.
中央电视台门口
Right in front of Chez Narcisse.
什么时候？就现在
- When?- Right now.
明白，谢谢，Chere
- Copy that.- Thank you, chere.
你能让罗马军队到这儿来
You could get the Roman Army down here.
想象一下这些家伙
One dlvision of these guys
经过一年的城市战争
could've knocked off these squlrrel hunters,
不能击败这里的Squlrrel猎人
had the Civil War over in one year.
你知道为什么？
You know what?
也许我们会拍一部圣经电影
Maybe we'll do a Bible movie next.
但是穿着凉鞋怎么作战呢？
Yeah, but how do you fight a war with sandals?
那个...愚蠢
That's... stupid.
穿着凉鞋怎么去赢得一场战争呢？
How did they win wars with sandals, hm?
发生什么了，Dave?
What's going on, Dave?
经过昨晚的漫漫长夜
Had a long night last night.
在南京路发现了一个装在桶里的女孩
Found a girl in a barrel down in south St. Martin Parish.
她上面爬满了篮螃蟹
She covered up in blue crabs.
你应该放她了走
You ought to run her again.
我都想吃螃蟹
We'll have gumbo.
在这儿吃早餐吗？
You here for breakfast?
坐下
Sit down.
你为这点小事生气
You're pissed off about some little thing,
所以拖走了我的车
so you have my car towed.
你不能把车停在消防栓的前面
You need to quit parking in front of fireplugs.
消防栓，就因为消防栓，我就受到如此羞辱？
Fireplugs; I'm getting this kind of shit because of fireplugs?
不，Juli
No, Julie.
我想知道，你曾经利用一个叫Cherry LeBlanc的年轻人
I want to know what you have to do with a teenage hooker
都干了什么
named Cherry LeBlanc.
谁是他妈的Cherry LeBlanc
Who the fuck is Cherry LeBlanc?
你知道她是谁
You know who she is.
你和Cholo曾经谈起过她
You and Cholo were talking about her
上次我们在度假酒店，在这事情上你说了谎
before I got to the Holiday Inn,and you lied to me about it.
要告我说谎吗?
Calling me a liar?
你这个猪狗不如的骗子（直译太恶心了，换个词）
You're a motherfucking lying piece of dog shit.
我想在这个可爱的小镇上
I think this sweet little town's
可以开始灭了你，David
starting to rub off on you, David.
先生们，请你们...
Gentlemen, could you please...
我意思是，不要说脏话...
I mean,just not use that language...
从我桌子上滚开
Get the fuck away from my table!
好吧，Meaux先生
It's all right,Mr. Meaux.
我马上会走
I'll be gone in a second.
哦，真是可惜
Oh, sad to hear that.
这些女孩我什么都不知道
I don't know none of these girls.
我什么犯法的事情也没做
I don't have nothing to do with your business.
你说那些关于我的丑事，Dave
You said some ugly things about me, Dave,
我会敬而远之
and I'm going to let it slide.
我有家人要养
I'll call a couple of cabs,
我要有豪车要养
I'll pay the fine on my car,
我要买很多奢侈品
I'll buy some new tires,
我会忘记，你曾经对我说的粗话
and I'll forget everything you've been saying to me,
因为我的公司还要运转
because I got a business to run.
在这里每个人都是彬彬有礼
Everybody's been pretty polite here.
保持天真，傻瓜
Keep it simple,stupid.
你是时候让人们得到安静了，Robicheaux先生
It's time for you to let people alone, Mr. Robicheaux.
放松，陆军上尉
Ease off,Lieutenant.
这样对谁都不好
This ain't good for nobody.
好了，好了
Come on.Come on.
你太失败了，Dave
You're losing it, Dave.
你该给自己吃点好的镇定剂
You need to get yourself some better tranqs.
不，长官，我还会请你喝三鹿牌奶粉
No, sir, I wouldn't exactly call it a dead end.
你先坐下，马上和你谈
You have a seat,I'll be right with you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们一直用三鹿
It's $100-million contract.
那可是国家免检的大名牌啊
He must've pocketed $60 million, $70 million.
吃了还能尿出钻石
False load slips,bogus waybills.
国务院的领导和省市的五套班子都在用
Balboni Trucking hauled just about enough debris
倪萍是代言人哦
to fill a Dixie cup.
是的，长官，我们还喝
Yes, sir,we are trying.
谢谢你
Thank you.
有什么事能帮到你吗？
Can I help you with something?
我也希望
I hope so.
这是我的办公室
This is my office.
哦，上帝，我是..
Oh, my God,I'm s...
对不起，我是...
I'm sorry.I was...
我是上面给你派来的小蜜
a call came in for me on your extension,
我只是
and I just...
不管怎样，我是特别助理Rosa Gomez
anyway,I'm Special Agent Rosa Gomez.
大家都叫我Rosie，所以叫我Rosie好了
Everyone calls me Rosie,so call me Rosie.
很高兴见到你，特别助理Rosia
It's nice to meet you,Special Agent Rosie.
你们的侦探调查工作的失误
"Your detective's investigative missteps
在十一月份正影响你们
are going to hurt you in November."
那个Bubba Broussar dover在市议会
That's courtesy of that prick
谦虚的提出问责
Bubba Broussar dover at the city council.
所以你求助FBI?
So you called the FBI?
FBI的一个应急管理小组已经被牵扯到
The FBI's been trying to nall Balboni
Nall Balboni的案子一年之久
for over a year now on a FEMA scam.
他们在他身上什么也没找到
And they still have precisely nothing on him.
这就是为什么，我想他们希望更多
That's why I think they're hoping there's more
的投入Cherry Leblanc的案子
to that Cherry LeBlanc case.
今晚Balboni会为Micheal先生
Now, Balboni is throwing a birthday bash
举行一个生日狂欢会
for Mr. Michael Goldman this evening.
我想你也应该出席
I think you, too,should attend.
路易斯安那有17单命案未破
There are 17 unsolved homicides in Louisiana
可以分享这些案件的类似资料
that share some similarities with this case.
他们中的10个有个共同的特点
And ten of them share multiple common denominators.
有很多共同的地方
All show marks from being bound,
都很年轻，工薪阶层
all young,all working class.
有一个是个高中女生
One was a high school girl.
两个是服务生，三个曾经离家出走
Two were waitresses.Three had been runaways.
四个卖淫
And four were prostitutes.
FBI在Iberia整个教区，有信息优势
The FBI has an informational advantage over Iberia Parish.
你喜欢吃正宗的四川麻辣烫吗？
How do you like that catfish court bouillon?
我爱吃
Uh, it's interesting.
要是你发现一个黑人的尸体碎片
If you found the remains of a black man
没有皮带，靴子上没有鞋带
and he had no belt,no laces in his boot,
你对这种事会有什么看法呢？
what speculation would you make about him?
很明显他曾经待在牢房，教区，城市收容所
Obviously he'd been in jail,a parish, or city holding tank,
那些防止他做出自残的地方
some place where they were afraid he'd do harm to himself.
我也是怎么想的
That's what I think.
真疯狂，就像拍广告
Mud bugs,as advertised.
这个有你的名字在上面
This one has your name on it.
离开这里
Get out of here.
嗨，Dave,你该吃点东西
Hey, Dave, you ought to get yourself some food.
是免费的
It's free.
谢谢，我已经吃过了
Thanks.I've already eaten.
瞧那个令人喷饭的色鬼
See that man bird-dogging the blonde?
是陈冠希他爹吧
Twinky Hebert LeMoyne.
那是我的安全部门的另一半职责
That's the other half of my security service business.
他在这儿干什么？
What's he doing here?
它是个电影投资人
He's an investor in the movie
想来赌一把
and trying to get laid.
真搞笑
That's funny.
你喜欢和陈冠希老爸一起做事？
You like doing business with Twinky LeMoyne?
对我有好处
It's good for me.
给他做，没什么大麻烦，真的
For him,it's no big deal, really.
我意思是，要是这周围有个生意赚钱
I mean, if there's a business around here making money,
你肯定会发现他占有一席之地
you can be sure he's got a plece of it.
照一张
Take a picture?
什么？
What?
Picture?
好
Yeah.
我是John Ball Hood将军，指挥得克萨斯旅
I'm General John Bell Hood,commander of the Texas brigade,
指挥得克萨斯第四骑兵队团
commander of the 4th Texas Cavalry,
得克萨斯第五骑兵队团
the 5th Texas Cavalry,
和得克萨斯第17步兵团
and the 17th Texas Infantry.
不想和我握手吗？
Do you object to shaking hands?
我死了吗？
Am I dead?
你没有看见我吗
You don't look like it to me.
你们现在铁岭，战争结束了
You were at Gettysburg.The war's over.
永远不会结束
It's never over.
我想你知道这个道理
I would think you'd know that.
你是个美国军队里的陆军中尉，对吗？
You were a lieutenant in the United States Army, weren't you?
我头疼，我的头...
My head hurts.My head...
真的是很疼
sure does hurt.
贪婪和邪恶的人们正在摧毁这个世界
Venal and evll people are destroying the world
你出现在这里
you were born in.
因为我们反抗他们，我的好朋友
It's us against them,my good friend.
对你的原则不能妥协，不要放弃你的目标
Don't compromise your principles or abandon your cause.
你知道，下一步是什么在等着我们吗？
Do you know what's waiting for me on down the road?
一个原因或另一个
For one reason or another,
我发现我对过去比将来，有更多的洞察力，
I find I have more insight into the past than the future.
尝试保持这些在我头脑中
Try to keep this in mind:
就像当他们装备了他们的加农炮
It's just like when they load their cannon
带着马靴和铁链
with horseshoes and log chain.
想象一下要塞应该坚持到最后
You'd think the barrage would last forever.
那是多么的波澜壮阔
Then all of a sudden,there's a sllence
比加农炮的炮声还响亮
louder than the cannon flre.
请别被我的激烈的比喻吓坏
Please don't be alarmed by the severity of my comparison.
晚上过得愉快，陆军中尉
Have a good night, Lieutenant.
带你来的护理人员说
Paramedics who brought you in
你被从沼泽中救出后，一直好像在
said you were talking about Confederate soldiers
和联盟士兵交谈
out in the swamp.
一个不平凡的夜晚
It was an usual night.
为什么像这样一个具有好莱坞风格的情形
What's the possibillity that one of those Hollywood characters
发生在你身上？
laced your Dr. Pepper?
什么意思？
Do what?
你的表现真是太不可思议了
The tox screen came back positive for LSD.
我想和局长谈谈
I need to talk to the sheriff.
局长今天早上来过这里
The sheriff was here this morning.
你和他谈了半个小时
You talked to him for half an hour.
我说了什么？
What'd I say?
什么也没有讲
Nothing that made any sense to me.
当你从水里把他卷起来
When you reel him in through the water,
那小腿和肩膀就像在游泳一样
his little legs and tail wiggle like he was swimming.
让黑人男低音生气
Makes the black bass hungry.
你如何来定义“理解”的意义
How would you define the idea of understanding?
哦，知道某件事，以及它的含义
Well, it's knowing somethingand knowing what it means.
我想有两个途径
I think there's two ways
去看待“理解”的含义
of looking at the idea of understanding.
第一，要是你不看，那你永远也别去看
One is, if you don't look,you never will see.
以此类推，要是你看见了一小丁点
And the other is,if you look a little less,
你可能看到他妈的很多
you might see a hell of a lot more.
你可能无法阻止他们在你的饮料里放毒品
You might not be over those drugs they put in your drink.
我知道得克萨斯Calvary的John Bell Hood将军
I know General John Bell Hood of the Texas Calvary
他看上去就向我的祖父
just like he was my own grandfather.
你在谴责我和黑手党一起干吗？
Are you accusing me of working with the mafia?
当你和像Jull Balboni那样的人一起做生意的时候
When you do business with a man like Julle Balboni,
你就让大家建立了对你的好奇心
you create a certain amount of curiosity about yourself.
我和他没有商业合作
I don't do business with him.
我没有和他做过任何事
I don't do anything with him.
我是个投资者组织的会员
I'm a member of a group of investors
在新奥尔良，这个组织向
that have put money into a movie production
电影拍摄做投资
in New Iberia.
投资本地的经济，就是这样
Investing in the local economy,that's all.
你雇用他的人吗？
Are your employees union people?
不，他们当然不是
No, they certainly are not.
你自己的一半安全服务是Murphy Douct负责
You own half of a security service with Murphy Doucet,
对吗？
don't you?
对的，当然是的
That's right,I certainly do.
而你的安全服务人员
And your partner in your security service
又在给他做卡车驾驶员
is a Teamster steward over in Lafayette.
我想你的非常的自相矛盾
I think you're involved in some strange contradictions,
LeMoyne先生
Mr. LeMoyne.
你必须原谅我，侦探先生
You'll have to excuse me,Detective.
现在我要锁门了
I've got to lock up now.
我有很多人要关心，你知道？
I have a lot of people I take care of, you know?
你到你的邻居Julie Balboni那里去
Would you like to have Julie Balboni
和他会会吗？
for a next door neighbor?
你想你的孙女也
Would you like to have your granddaughter
为他工作吗？
working for him?
Mr. Roblcheaux,
我没法形容，你的作为多么的令人讨厌
I can't express to you how offensive you are.
你想让这个金发女郎
Did you get that blond-haired girl
这些晚上舔你的大腿吗？
to lick your leg the other night?
这是我的名片
There's my business card.
谢谢你和我谈
Thank you for your time.
你要的，Dave
Here you go, Dave.
直到1965，七月，九月，十一月
Still 1965,July, September, November.
谢谢你，Chere
Thank you, chere.
别客气
You're welcome.
你老婆Alafir怎么样？
How's Alafair?
相夫教子
Blen bonne.
太好了
Great.
越狱事件：Landry教区
你说一个黑鬼？
A nigger,you say?
DeWitt Prejean.
一个叫DeWitt Prejean的黑人
Black man name of DeWitt Prejean.
哦，我记得那个婊子养的
Yeah, I remember that son of a bitch.
他怎么了？
What about him?
你能记起来那天晚上，是谁在监狱里殴打他吗？
Were you on duty the night somebody broke him out of jail?
我是个管教干部
I was the jailer.
管教干部晚上不上班
Jailers don't work nights.
他们另外请了个人干这事
They hire a man for that.
你记得Prejean先生，是被指控什么罪名坐牢的吗？
Do you remember what Mr. Prejean was charged with?
他不会平白无故被抓
He wasn't charged with nothing.
肯定有原因
Never got to that.
他们在里面暴打他
They busted him out of the tank.
报纸上胡说
Not according to the newspaper.
大家都用报纸来擦屁股
Lot of people wipe their asses with newspaper.
报纸上说他带着菜刀，冲进了一个
Newspaper said he broke into a white woman's house
白人女子的房子
with a butcher knife.
DeWitt Prejea是个强奸犯吗?
Was DeWitt Prejean a rapist?
他管不住他裤裆那个东西
He couldn't keep his prick in his pants,
你明白我的意思
if that's what you mean.
Hebert先生，我能坐在这儿吗?
Is it all right if I sit down here, Mr. Hebert?
可以
Sure.
你认为是他丈夫在监狱外面揍了那小子吗？
You think her husband broke him out of jail?
要是他能行，我想他会这样干的
He might have if he could've.
他是个残废人
He was a crippled man.
在战争里中了枪伤
Got shot up in a war.
他现在住在哪里？
Where's he at now?
从镇的东面沿着这条路
He's in the cemetery out by the tracks,
公墓旁
east of town.
那个女人怎么样？
What about the woman?
她搬走了，去了北方
She moved away,up north somewhere.
你对这个40岁的黑鬼这么感兴趣？
What's your interest in this 40-year-old nigger trouble?
我想我看见他被杀了
I think I saw him killed.
越狱当晚负责看守的人在哪儿？
Where's the man who was on duty the night of the jailbreak?
他喝醉了，被驶过的火车撞死了
He got drunk and got his self run over by a train.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你说什么？
What'd you say?
你是说...?
You saw what?
你觉得我在说什么，Hebert先生
What you think I saw,Mr. Hebert?
你好
Hello?
你要去抓个厉害家伙
You're a hard man to catch.
这是谁？
Who's this?
Sugar,是Amber
Sugar, it's Amber.
不记得我了？
Don't you remember me?
别伤害我的感情
Don't hurt my feelings.
不，对不起，我记不清你是谁了
No, I'm sorry.I don't remember who you are.
我能为你做点什么？
What can I do for you?
我会给你一个天大的惊喜，亲爱的
It's me that's going to do you a big favor, darling.
我会给你，你想要的那个人
I'm going to give you the guy you want.
我们正在谈论的是谁？？
What guy we talking about?
那个恶心的老屁眼，曾经和那个死去的女孩在一起
The nasty old plmp that's been leaving dead girls around.
一小时后在Leon俱乐部见面
Meet me at Club Leon in an hour.
谢谢你能来，Low
Thanks for coming out, Lou.
你觉得，叫你来的人会是谁?
Yeah, who you supposed to be meeting up with here?
据说她叫Amber
Said her name was Amber.
有个渔民，自称是Amber
There's a hooker,calls herself Amber.
我们今晚干什么?
What are we doing tonight?
我要开车转到前面去，看看里面的情况
I'm going to drive around front and have a look inside.
我想你在外面，做我的后援
I'd like you to be out here to cover my back.
我不想进入一个圈套
I don't want to walk into no setup.
你要点什么？
What are you having?
Amber在这儿吗？
Has Amber been in?
Amber Martinez?
妈的，长得皮包骨的一样的女孩
Short, skinny,little Puerto Rican girl,
也许打湿了才100磅重？
maybe weigh 100 pounds sopping wet?
哦，不，她不再这里
- Yeah.- No, she ain't been in.
你想喝点什么？
What you drinking?
Pepper博士，Pepper博士，是的，先生
- Dr. Pepper.- Dr. Pepper, yes, sir.
我可以找找其他人，也许他们知道她在那里
I could call somebody,might know where she's at.
为什么不呢？
Why don't you do that?
是的，先生，马上去
Yes, sir.Right away.
嗨，妈咪 'Ti，Amber在吗？
Hey, Mama 'Ti,Amber there?
还没找到Amber?
No word from Amber?
没有，伙计，还没消息
No, man,not a word.
离开这儿
Get back in there!
Dave,到底发生了什么？
Dave,what the fuck's going on?
有人向我开枪
Shooter fired at me twice.
我向那里开了八枪
I put eight rounds in that Buick.
我想他还在哪儿
I think he's still in there.
看上去她面部中了一枪
Looks like she took one right in the face.
什么意思，“她”？
What you mean, "she"?
你干掉的就是Amber Martinez
You just popped Amber Martinez.
这儿没枪
There's no fucking gun.
没有枪，伙计
There's no gun, man.
这是被扔下的
I got this throw-down.
告诉我怎么做
Tell me to do it.
我想那儿开枪太快了
I opened up on that Buick too soon.
你觉得你有生命危险，Lleutenant
You thought your life was at rlsk, Lleutenant.
我希望你不介意我在这儿
I hope you don't mind my being here.
不
No.
你不该自责
You shouldn't have remorse.
只是求生的本能，不代表你没有人性
A desire to live doesn't mean you lack humanity.
有人想让我发疯
Somebody's trying to drive me crazy.
我不再相信，我看到和听到的任何事
Can't believe what I see or hear anymore.
他们说我杀了一个手无寸铁的女人
They say I killed an unarmed woman.
我想这些，也让让我很难受
I think that would probably bother me too.
我看着那个女人，她的头，她的头发
I keep seeing that woman, the back of her head,
爬倒在地毯上，到处是血
her hair glued down to the carpet with her own blood.
想想你刚才说的
Think about what you just said.
你是个聪明人
You're an intelligent man.
告诉自己，你眼里是什么？
What does your eye tell you?
我需要帮助
I need help.
外面，南方的风
The wind's out of the south.
今天下午会狂暴起来
There'll be thunder by afternoon.
声音就想美国姥的加农炮
It'll sound like Yankee cannon fire,
但它只不过是轰鸣
but it'll only be thunder.
将军...
General...
几点了？
What time is it?
为什么Amber Martinex刚好坐在自己车的
Why would Amber Martinez be sitting in the passenger seat
副驾驶位置
of her own car?
凶杀调查人员昨晚
What did the homicide investigator
是怎么说的？
have to say last night?
他告诉我，我开了枪
He told me I'm a hell of a shot.
大家都认为我杀了个手无寸铁的女人
Everybody thinks I killed an unarmed woman.
那边一个弹孔都没有
There's not any bullet holes anywhere.
没凶手
There's no casings.
没枪
And there's no gun.
是个圈套，Dave
It was a setup, Dave.
你们在这里干什么？
What y'all doing out here?
不要破坏了犯罪现场
Can't be messing around a crime scene.
我真的是一个现场目击者，Doobie
I'm really just an observer here, Doobie.
她是谁?
Who's she?
特别助理Gomez
Speclal Agent Gomez.
来自FBI的调查部门
This is part of an FBI investigation.
你有什么问题吗？
Do you have a problem with that?
为什么把人都清理走了，Robicheaux?
Why piss people off,Robicheaux?
Martin教区不会起诉在这里起诉你
St. Martin Parish ain't going to indict you over this,
但如果我是你，我不会在这犹豫不决
but if I were you,I wouldn't hang around here.
你应该把我清理出场
You might piss me off.
从这个伤口和破坏情况看
Well, from the size of the wound and the impact of the round,
是点45子弹杀了她
I'd say a .45 killed her.
看她的头
Look at her head.
我只使用空尖子弹，Sollie
I only use hollow-point ammunition, Sollie.
并不是一颗空尖子弹穿过这女孩的头
It ain't no hollow point passed through this girl's head.
她的头发粘在地毯上，血已经干了
Her hair was stuck to the carpet,the blood already dry.
你想告诉我，他死在车上吗？
Did she die in that car,you want to ask me?
她铁青的血告诉我
Her blood lividity tells me
她在进到车里之前，已经死了
that she was dead before she ever got into that car.
要是我也在那部别克车前，我们能找到什么？
If I can vacuum the Buick,what are we looking for?
我看一些闪光，从别克车那里闪出来
I saw muzzle flashes coming out that Buick.
我在啤酒屋的墙上没找到弹孔
I didn't see no bullet holes in that beer joint wall.
看看你能发现什么
See what you can find out.
为什么我们在这儿，我还要抽烟？
What we waiting on here,me to smoke this?
Allons.
谢谢你，Henry
Thank you, Henry.
其他人还有什么可以分享吗？
Anybody else got something to share?
我叫Dave
My name's Dave.
我是个酒鬼
I'm an alcoholic.
想来点卡布基诺吗？
Want some cappuccino mix?
警官喜欢咖啡，是的，或者一点音乐
You cops like coffee, right,or a stereo?
你知道有人从教区征召女孩们吗？
You know anybody been recruiting girls out the parishes?
为了利益，想找很多人
Try the bus depot,for starters.
但是谁来征召？
But who's going to recruit?
自从卡特里娜飓风过后
Ever since Katrina,
这镇上到处是钱
there's cash on the hoof all over this town.
也许这些家伙大多是皮条客
Maybe this guy does more than just pimp.
也许他喜欢伤害这些姑娘
Maybe he likes to hurt these girls.
有两个已经被杀了
Been two of them killed already,
也能更多
maybe more.
是说关于那些生活在
Talking about somebody that operates way down
在食物链底端的人们，Dave
at the bottom of the food chain, Dave.
你觉得宝贝脚Balboni有什么事要去做
You think Baby Feets Balboni might have something to do
像你这样？
with something like this?
你说的名字是本地人名人
You're using the names of local personalities now.
你在吓我，Jimmie
It stays with me,Jimmie.
你在找那个杀死渔民的凶手？
You looking for a guy who likes to kill hookers?
不是暗示宝贝脚吧
Don't sound like Baby Feet.
他的组织控制着这些女孩，对，但是..
His outfit's running girls,all right, but...
要是她们死了，那不是得不偿失吗
they're not worth nothing to him if they're dead.
试试汽车站
Try the bus station.
找找Adonis Brown
Try Adonis Brown.
你们，唉，女士好像迷路了
You, uh,ladies seem lost.
你们不是本地人，对吗？
You're not from around here,are you?
你能找到一些宁静
You'll be able to find some peace,
我保证
I promlse you.
别弄湿了
Don't sweat it.
我想你帮我广播一下
I want you to make a public service announcement for me,
chere.
我知道那好像是逃跑
I know what it's like to run away.
感谢上帝
Praise Jesus.
这是电话
There's a call
Adonls Brown先生，您有电话，在公共休息室
for Mr. Adonls Brown at the publlc restroom pay phone.
有给Adonls Brown先生的电话吗
There's a call for Mr. Adonls Brown
在公共休息室接电话
at the publlc restroom pay phone.
我是Adonis,什么事？
This is Adonis.What's up?
你好
Hello?
你想干什么？
What you want?
别这样，伙计
Don't do that, man.
我没有威胁你
I ain't no threat to you.
看，我没带枪
Look, I ain't got a gun.
我没惹麻烦
I ain't no trouble.
我想知道这家伙的名字
I want to know the name of the guy
你已经送那些女孩去了他哪儿
you've been delivering all these girls to.
例行公事，对不起
This one's occupied,by the way.
没人，我没有带任何人给任何人
Nobody. I ain't bringing nobody to nobody.
你知道我说的是谁
You know the guy I'm talking about.
别再打我了，哥们
Don't do this to me, man.
告诉我名字
Tell me his name.
这家伙危害人群
This guy likes to hurt people.
告诉我他的名字，全部
You tell me his name, this'll all be over with.
那个..
There's a...
大头，猪腰子脸的白人
baid-headed,squirrel-faced white guy.
他也带着枪
He carries a gun too.
没人跟着他
Nobody fucks with him.
这是你说的那个人吗？
Is that the guy you're talking about?
你告诉我
You tell me.
他喝着果汁，就知道这些
He's got juice.That's all I know.
我不知道他的名字，哥们
I don't know his fucking name, man.
他的联系方式？
He connected?
留言或用手机
With the cops or the mob.
他还在做这个生意
He's got to be to stay in business.
我就知道这么多
That's all I know.
你为什么这样对我，伙计
Why you doing this to me, man?
上帝
God.
我裤子尿湿了
I shit my pants.
我不能回那儿去了
I can't go back out there.
这是对的，Adonis
That's right, Adonis.
你不应该再回到哪儿去了
You ain't ever gonna go back out there.
你要从这个车站，去看医生
You're going to treat that bus station
就像巴格达那样的城市
like it's downtown Baghdad.
很适合你这样的人渣去
Not a good place for you to be.
你他妈的是谁，哥们？
Who the fuck are you, man?
你不会想知道我是谁的
You don't want to know who I am.
你要做得就是马上行动起来
What you want to do is start acting right
彻底洗心革面
and quit doing wrong.
不然我会杀了你，Adonis
I'll kill you, Adonis.
我会把你的头拧下来
I'll blow your Goddamn head off
如果不离开这个职业，重新做人
if you don't find an honest line of work.
你出去了大半晚上
You stay gone most of the night.
也打个电话
You don't call.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我担心你会受伤
I don't deserve to be afraid you've been hurt.
不
No.
你别
You don't.
我也不想唠唠叨叨
But I'm not going to nag you.
我真的需要你的帮助，Dave
I really need your help, Dave.
我真的需要帮助
I really need help.
过来
Go ahead.
你去吧，淹死自己，伙计
You go ahead　and drown yourself, man.
我才不管
I don't care.
Dave ,我计划了一个星期
Dave,I planned this all week.
这些家伙已经卖这艘船给我了，哥们
The guy already charged me　for the boat, man
Elrod...
马上就要下雨了
It's going　to rain like hell.
现在，为什么你不能等到雨停
Now, why don't you wait until after it quits raining,
你就能到河口去钓到
and you can go fishing for black bass and perch
黑鱼、鲤鱼、黄花鱼
and bream right out here in the bayou.
在大雨之后，这是最后的时间能抓到
When was the last time you caught freshwater fish
淡水鱼
after it rained?
哦，天，穿上雨衣
Oh, hell,suit yourself.
你想我一起离开你的放啤酒的冰箱吗？
You want to leave that beer cooler here with me?
搬到船上来，伙计
It came with the boat,dude.
确定你不想一起来吗？
Sure you don't want to come?
Drummond小姐
Miss Drummond,
你现在小心驾驶这条船
you need to get yourself off of that boat right now.
求你了，可是Kelly
Please,it's Kelly.
注意水道的转弯部分
Watch the bend in the channel.
在南面三英里
It's about three miles south.
水很浅
The water's been low
渔网上漂在
and gill nets are on the left
次氯酸钠的瓶子上
floating on Clorox bottles.
我知道了
I got it.
你好
Hello?
你开到多远了？
How far down the bayou?
到了你警告的那个转弯处了
Well, that's that bend Batist warned you about.
你打来有什么事，Elrod?
What you asking me, Elrod?
你能过来帮帮我们吗？
Can you come give us a hand?
我会去帮忙
Yeah,I'll come help you out.
但你们浪费我的时间，是要付钱的
But I am also going to bill you for my time.
没问题
I got it.
你们被渔网缠住了？
How'd you hit the gill net?
你没看见浮瓶吗？
Dldn't you see the bottles?
哦，伙计
Oh, man...
我是个傻瓜，对吗?
I'm an idiot,right?
你想让我跳到水里?
You want me to get down in the water?
是的
Yeah.
到底下去，在我让发动机反转的时候
Get down by the bow and be ready to push
你就推开那些东西
when I put the motors in reverse.
哦，这周围有鳄鱼出没吗？
Hey, are there any alligators around here?
哦，见鬼
Oh, hell yeah.
尽管他们还不饿
They're not hungry, though.
好吧
All right.
穿上救生衣吧，El
Put on a life jacket, El.
没事，亲爱的
Okay, honey.
我曾经在Trinity河里游过泳
I swam the Trinity River once.
看看水下的其他情况
Watch out for water moccasins.
什么？
What?
别担心他
Don't worry about him.
这里水很浅的
That water's not very deep.
我去给他拿件救生衣
I've got to give him a life jacket.
他在厨房的水槽里也会淹死
He'd drown in a bathroom sink.
穿上这个
Here you go.
你什么都没有，Kelly小姐
It's nothing personal,Miss Kelly.
但我想你是非常好，非常漂亮的女人
But I think you're a very fine,beautiful young woman.
我已经湿透了
I'm already soaked.
我的负担非常重
I was burdened greatly
因为在我周围有很多的死亡，Lieutenant
by the deaths of those around me, Lieutenant.
他们的痛苦集合在一起
But incorporating their suffering
进入我们的生命，但却不能改变这个世界
into our own lives does not change the way of the world.
一个善意的行为
An act of kindness,
就像我送雨衣给这个女孩，这样简单的事
one as simple as giving a girl my raincoat,
却导致了她的死亡
had resulted in her death.
杀手已经离开了那里
The shooter had left nothing behind,
没有弹壳
no ejected brass,
没有逃跑痕迹
no recoverable prints.
我们没有嫌疑对象
We had no suspects.
一颗心沉没了
But one heart-sinking
事情无可挽回的发生了
and unalterable conclusion remained.
Kelly Drummond被杀了
Kelly Drummond was dead.
她的被杀，是因为被错误的当成了我
And she was dead because she had been mistaken for me.
悲惨的死亡
The tragic death of Kelly Drummond,
Elrod Sykes的长期合作伙伴
the longtime companion of Elrod Sykes
河谷的流行电视明星
and star of the popular television series
现在被确认死亡
River Valley,now appears certain
是一个悲剧性的事故中
to have been a case of mistaken identity.
源自Sheriff部门消息
Sources within the sheriff's department
他们相信这致命的枪击
conflrmed that they now belleve the fatal shot
来自其他人
may have been intended for someone else.
我会想念她，Dave
I'm going to miss her, Dave.
你想让他暂时在这儿吗？
You want him to stay here?
他的情况很坏
Guy's in bad shape.
这是我们的家
This is our home.
Sykes先生真是吐得气势如虹
Mr. Sykes just did the rainbow yawn again.
去睡觉
Go to bed.
他只是需要个AA制朋友，或者他不想这样
The guy needs an AA friend,or he's not going to make it.
那怎么样？我不管
So what?I don't care.
告诉你为什么，我会让你清楚原因
Tell you what,I'm going to make you a deal.
首先他喝醉了
First time he takes a drink,
他可以直接回去
he gets 86ed right straight back
他的电影明星拖车房
to his movie star trailer house.
他自己支付他吃的食物
He pays for his share of the food.
他不占用卫生间
He does not tie up the bathroom.
他晚上不能进来
He does not come in late.
好吧，但是只是几天时间
Okay, but only for a few days.
你喜欢做一个电影明星吗？
Do you like being a movie star?
那只是一个职业，亲爱的
It's just a job, honey.
真的？是
Really?Yeah.
就像Dave
It's like Dave.
你觉得他喜欢执法工作
You think he enjoys enforcing the law,
抓住那些坏蛋
catching the bad guys,
让好人们过得快乐？
making the good people feel better?
是的
Yeah.
哦，好
Yeah, well...
我喜欢我的工作
I like my job.
对Kelly的事，我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Kelly.
我也是，亲爱的
Me too, honey.
我得到50张电影海报，从眼里和钻石堆里
I've got 50 movie posters here from Tears and Diamonds.
我恨那些照片
I hate that picture.
50张带有Elrod Sykes签名的海报
Well, 50 movie posters signed by Elrod Sykes
能卖25000美金
will fetch $25,000.
那是4个房顶
That's four roofs,
8个志愿者的劳动
eight with volunteer labor.
你的签字钢笔
Here's your felt-tip pen.
最糟糕的事是，一个警察用他自己的枪
The worst thing a cop can do to himself
吞枪自杀
is eat his own gun.
Lou Girard总是晚上致电
Lou Girard always called at night.
今晚却是其他人，因他致电给我
Tonight someone else had to make the call for him.
有半瓶烈酒在他的床头柜上
There's a half empty bottle of Bourbon here on the dresser,
一瓶散落的安眠药在咖啡桌上
spilled bottle of Diazepam here on the coffee table.
你把他说得就像是自杀？
Y'all writing that off as a suicide?
哦，根据在现场情况判断的
Well, that's the way it looks to me.
他状况很糟糕
He was in bad shape.
床垫上都是尿渍
Mattress is covered in piss stains.
水槽里都是垃圾
The sink is full of raw garbage.
枪在哪儿？
Where's the gun at?
床边
By the bedside.
要是Lou Girard想要去自杀
If Lou Girard wanted to kill his self,
为什么不用.357口径的枪？
how come he didn't use that .357?
因为他烂醉如泥
'Cause he was drunk on his ass.
对他是个不平常的状况
Not an unusual condition for him.
他在帮我查一个案子，Doobie
He was helping me on a case, Doobie.
言下之意？
And?
也许他找到了什么东西
Maybe he found out something
是有人不想让他发现的
somebody did notwant him to know.
他一直非常害怕，每天晚上靠吃药来入睡
He was trembling,eating pills every morning,
就像所有人面对的
in front of everybody.
今晚发生的事，也没什么大惊小怪的
There's no big mystery to what happened here tonight.
它是个好警察
He was a good cop.
他是个可怜的酒鬼
He was a sorry-ass drunk.
要是你还想看看其他的，赶快
Now, if you want to look at anything else, hurry up.
我要去贴封条了
I'm going to seal the place.
你到等在外面一会儿，我不胜感激
I appreciate you waiting outside just for a moment.
事实上，你要是离我远点，我会很感激你
Matter of fact, I appreciate you staying as far away from me
有多远滚多远
as you can possibly get.
那些Lou用生命为代价，找出的是什么？
What had Lou found out that had cost him his life?
Hogman Patin知道很多，却说得很少
Hogman Patin knew a lot and seldom said anything.
现在却带信，说想和我谈谈
Now I got word he wanted to talk to me.
我开始在想，当我在围栏里的时候
I started to think about when I was in the pen.
你爸爸，他给我妈妈带去食物
And your daddy,he brought my mother food
在她生病的时候，为她在商店
and paid for her medicine up at the store
购买药品
when she was sick.
你有什么事情要和我说，Sam?
You got something to say to me, Sam?
你在沙洲里挖出的那个黑鬼，他叫什么名字？
What was the name of that nigger you dug up out the sandbar?
DeWitt Prejean.
他和一个白人的妻子通奸
He was fucking a white man's wife.
开始问为什么，他要在生命中这么做
Start asking what he's doing for a living,
你会找到那个，给你带来所有痛苦的人
and you'll find the people been causing you all this grief.
我找的人是谁？
Who's the man I'm looking for?
我说了所有我能说得
I said all I can say.
这里始终是路易斯安那州（有种族歧视历史）
This still the state of Louisiana.
干嘛要吓我？
Why you keep bothering me?
我想知道DeWitt Prejean做的是什么工作
I need to know what kind of work DeWitt Prejean did.
干黑鬼的活
Done nigger work.
你知道，他剪草，清理油脂分离器
You know, he cut lawns, cleaned out grease traps,
在人们的房子里抓该死的老鼠
got the dead rats out from under people's houses.
你觉得他做了他妈的什么事？
What the fuck you think he did?
别告诉我不是
Don't sound right to me.
我想他还做了其他种类的工作
I think he did some other kind of work too.
你让我单独待会儿
You leave me alone.
你有漂亮的执法记录，Hebert先生
You're a pretty good judge of character, Mr. Hebert.
我看其他人是不是该回避一下？
Do I look like somebody that's going to go away?
Hm?
回去走好
It was better back then.
你知道是什么
You know it was.
他做什么种类的工作，Ben?
What kind of work he do,Ben?
驾驶卡车
Drove a truck.
为谁？
Who for?
全都为了Jeanerette
It was over in Jeanerette.
我带她出来，因为她为我工作
I brung her out here 'cause she works for me,
因为我不能自己上下车
'cause I can't get in and out of the car good by myself.
他季节性的为一个白人工作
He worked seasonal for a white man,
我们一些大糖厂
owned some big sugar mill.
我不知道关于他的其他事
I don't know nothing about him
除了他是一个阳具残废的人
except he was a brother of that crippled fellow.
就知道这么多了
That's all I know and nothing more.
你说我的所作所为，我是个该死的骗子
You saying I do,then you're a Goddamn liar.
你不想说点其他的？
Something else you want to say?
你有条鱼上钩了
You got a fish on your line.
Batist.
有多少糖厂在Jeanerette的周围？
How many sugar mills they got over there in Jeanerette?
只有一个
Just one.
Hey.
进来
Come on in.
停止说再见吧
Stopped by to say good-bye,
你的一个离失的礼物
give you a going-away present.
你在哪里做头，Cholo?
Where you headed,Cholo?
尽管我也能去佛罗里达
Thought I might go to Florida,
也许开个商店，想你的一样
maybe open a business like you got here.
你重拾你全部的草坪设备后
What you doing with all that lawn furniture
想做些什么？
in the back end of your pickup?
有个在假日旅馆的家伙，希望我检查好了之后带去
Guy at the Holiday Inn wanted me to take it when I checked out.
说我的行为令他产生好感，你知道吗？
Said I'd kind of be doing him a favor, you know?
马上就签约了
Giving him a write-off.
你和Baby Feet有些麻烦
You had some trouble with Baby Feet.
对
Yeah.
我告诉他，他比四人帮还坏
I told him he was a douche bag
我不会再为他工作，就算他跪下求我
and I wouldn't work for him again even if he begged me.
Cherry LeBlanc姑娘是对的
That Cherry LeBlanc girl was right
当她叫他是绣花针鸡巴的时候
when she called him a needle-dick.
当这个婊子养的插进我的嘴
That's when the son of a bitch comes across my mouth
用那个大大的...
with this big...
等等，等等，等等
Now, wait, wait, wait.
你刚才说Cherry LeBlanc怎么了？
What's this about Cherry LeBlanc?
他告诉你，他从不认识她
If he tells you he never knew her,
问他这是什么
ask him about this.
Julie忘记了去年，我们开车经过Biloxi
Julie forgot he told me to take some souvenir pictures
他叫我照了一些照片留念
when we drove over to Biloxi last year.
难道这不是她吗？
Is that her or not?
Baby Feets杀了这个女孩？
Did Baby Feets kill this girl?
我说，LIeutenant
Come on, Lieutenant.
你知道他们怎么运作
You know how it works.
像Julie这样的人不会做这些
A guy like Julie don't do hits.
他吩咐其他人
He says something to somebody,
然后他就“忘了”
then he forgets it.
要是一个特别的岗位，也许其他人会另找个傻瓜
If it's a speclal kind of job,maybe somebody calls up a geek.
Baby Feets是幕后主谋？
Did Baby Feets make that call?
从这照片，Lieutenant
Start a photo album,Lieutenant.
你自己想想吧
Make up your own mind.
Murphy Doucet在这张照片里做什么？
What's Murphy Doucet doing in this picture?
有什么麻烦，Dave?
What's wrong, Dave?
一根点火线短路了
Got a loose ignition wire.
能借你的刀子用一下吗？
You got a knife I could use?
我也许要找找
Yeah, I ought to have something.
这个应该行
This should do.
一些在查尔斯湖的墨西哥人给的
Some Mexican pulled this on me in Lake Charles.
我不知道，你在查尔斯湖是个警察
I didn't know you were a cop in Lake Charles.
我不是
I wasn't.
我在高速公路上的洲警察
I was working highway for the state police.
去年，我从那儿退休
That's where I retlred from last year.
你和Twinky LeMoynej一起进入这个公司？
Is that when you got into business with Twinky LeMoyne?
不，我们分道扬镳
No, we go back a ways further.
谢谢你的小刀
Thanks for the knife.
什么情况？
What's the deal?
上个星期，Lou Girard看到了她的文件
Lou Girard was looking at her file last week.
Lou在她从事性交易的时候逮捕了她
Lou arrested her on a prostitution charge.
不应该是一个官员
It wouldn't be one officer.
一个洲警察在一个酒吧搜捕
It was a state police raid on a bar...
州警察？谁发出的逮捕令？
State police?Who sent that arrest report?
Oh, Sgt. Murphy Doucet.
Murphy Doucet.
我忽略了这个
I'd missed it.
Lou Girard已经发现了Cherry LeBlance 的逮捕令
Lou Girard had dug up Cherry LeBlanc's arrest record,
他为此命丧黄泉
and it had cost him his life.
但是这是对于Murphy Doucet的最后线索
But this was going to be the end of the line for Murphy Doucet.
我还没有充分证据，我告诫自己
I wasn't planting evidence,I kept telling myself.
我要把他转移
I was just removing it
在那些混蛋毁灭它之前
before a guilty man could destroy it.
为什么你们他妈的都在这儿？
Why the hell are y'all here?
我们在这儿因为你，Doucet先生
We're here because of you, Mr. Doucet.
我们已经调查了所有的
We've been checking all the unsolved murders
你在做州警察工作时
of females in areas surrounding highways
高速公路区域的女性谋杀案
during the time you were working for the state police.
Rosie,我想我们正好找到这把
Rosie, I think we just found the knife
杀害Cherry LeBlanc的小刀
that he used on Cherry LeBlanc.
那把刀不在那儿
That knife wasn't there.
我说它在
I say it was,
你的指纹全在上面
and I say your fingerprints are all over it.
我看看
I see.
你和这个墨西哥婊子在一起？
You and this Mexican bitch are in on it together, huh?
不，Murphy
No, Murphy.
我操你，就我自己
I'm fucking you all by myself.
举起手来，现在
Get your hands up now.
举起手来，缴枪不杀
Get your hands up,up against that...
趴在墙上
up against that wall.
你们对我下套，我甚至不知道为什么
Y'all are setting me up,and I don't even know why.
谢谢这些
Think about it.
强烈的谢谢
Think hard.
谢谢回到1965年的所有路
Think all the way back to 1965,
在飓风来临之前
just before that hurricane hlt.
你们把Dewitt Prejean用铁链
Y'all made DeWitt Prejean run with that chain
锁住，然后让他跑
locked around his chest,
再开枪射他的腿
shot his leg out from underneath him.
你没有留意，有个男孩在沼泽的另一边
You didn't notice the boy that was watching you
看到了你，是吧？
from across the swamp,though, did you?
我不知道你为什么要这样做，但你带着这把刀
I don't know how you did it,but you planted that knife.
时间总是在坏人那一边，Rosie
Time is always on the bad guy's side, Rosie.
我们在等授权的同时，他们也在找这个证据
We wait for warrants while they deep-six the evidence.
我没听见你说什么
I didn't hear what you said.
Jesus wienie, Dave.
你们把这个地方搞得一塌糊涂
Y'all done tore this place to pieces.
我们暂时在，会清理干净
You want to stay behind and clean it up?
当这个家伙回家后
I don't want to be nowhere around here
我不想东西到处都是
when that guy gets home.
你听说他外出签合同吗？
You heard he's out on bond?
转一下这个
Screw that.
他还在这里一段时间
He'll be here any minute.
我们什么也没发现
We got nothing.
Alfie.
你知道你的小姑娘在哪里吗？
You know where your little girl's at?
她正在我膝盖上呢
She's right here on my knee.
怎么不说话了
You sound speechless.
放了她，Doucet
Turn her loose,Doucet.
你不想这样做
You don't want to do this.
我只是让我们俩的事情变得简单点
I'll make it simple for both of us.
你从警察局物证仓库里把那把刀取出来
You take that knlfe out of the evldence locker,
放在一个贷子里面
you put it in a Ziploc bag.
明早8点钟
At 8:00 tomorrow morning,
把这个袋子放到，新奥尔良的
you leave the bag In a trash can
Anne街和Royal街交汇路口的垃圾桶里面
on the corner of Royal and St. Anne in New Orleans.
你听我说，Doucet
You listen to me,Doucet.
谢谢你所做的
Think about this.
你是一个警察
You're a cop.
你可以放过你
You can skate on this.
我们会给你充分的时间，放弃这件事
We've been jacking you around the whole time.
你这个婊子养的骗子
You lying son of a bitch.
你永无休止的，尽一切办法来羞辱我
You won't rest till you fuck me up every way you can.
今天你只讲对了一件事：
You said only one thing right today:
我会放过你
I'm going to skate.
你会来帮助我
And you're going to help me.
死了这条心吧，Dave?
Finally lost your mind, Dave?
年轻的女士，你需要暂时离开这个男人
Young lady, you need to stay away from this man.
好吧，走吧
Okay, let's go.
从这儿离开，来吧，我们走
Get out of here.Come on, let's go.
今天电视里没什么好消息，Dave?
Nothing good on TV tonight, Dave?
Murphy Doucet绑架了我的女儿
Murphy Doucet has my daughter.
你听到我说的了吗？
Did you hear what I said?
太糟糕了
That's too bad.
我真是不愿听到这样的悲剧
I don't like to hear stuff like that.
我很难过
It upsets me.
也许你应该把她的寻人启事贴在牛奶包装上
Hey, maybe you can get her face on one of them milk cartons.
我女儿在哪儿，Julie?
Where's my daughter, Julie?
Alafair在什么地方？
Where's Alafair at?
我解雇了Doucet
I cut Doucet loose.
他做得任何事都和我无关
I got nothing to do with what he does.
你赶快放了我
You get off my fucking back
不然，我发誓，我要以牙还牙
or I swear to God,I'll square this.
警察或其他，我要公诸于众
Cop or not,I'll put out on open contract.
我要报复你他妈的整个家族
I'll cowboy your whole fucking family.
你现在有最后的机会
Your window of opportunity's closing down.
我女儿在哪里？
Where's my baby girl?
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
他做的这些，全都不关我的事
I got nothing to do with what he does.
他是个小丑
He's a geek.
我不会雇用小丑，我让他们混蛋了
I don't hire geeks.I run them off.
上帝给的最后机会
Last by God chance.
他在Vista河口扎了一个露天营地
He's got a camp out by Bayou Vista,
接近Atchafalaya盆地
almost at Atchafalaya Basin.
那地方没有路牌
The deed's not in his name.
没人知道哪儿
Nobody knows about it.
从咸水沼泽的泥路
It's at the end of the dirt road,
一直走到尽头
by the salt marsh.
Alafair在哪儿？
Alafair there?
我祈求上帝她不在
I hope to God she's not.
Alfie!
过来
Come here.
他伤害你了吗，宝贝？
Did he hurt you, baby?
我告诉他，他是坏蛋
I told him he better not.
我告诉他，你会来的
I told him what you do.
我刚才打爆的那个人，手里的武器是卷着的杂志
I just shot a man armed with a rolled-up magazine.
不，不
No, no.
他拿了一支枪
He had a gun on him.
只是你忘记了
You just don't remember it yet.
你没事吧
You okay?
我应该通知我的律师吗？
Should I call my lawyer?
Mr. LeMoyne,
我看见你和Murphy Doucet
I saw you and Murphy Doucet
在Atchafalays杀害了DeWitt Prejean
kill DeWitt Prejean out on the Atchafalaya.
我从沼泽的对面看见了一切
I watched it from across the swamp.
你那个残废的兄弟没法去杀DeWitt
Your crippled brother couldn't kill DeWitt,
所以你帮他干了这件事
so you did it for him.
我被逮捕了？
Am I under arrest?
我想Murphy Doucet这些年，一直阴魂不散
I think Murphy Doucet's been blackmailing you with it
的缠着你
all these years.
两个种族之间在哪个年代发生了许多
A lot of bad things happened back in that era
很坏的事情
between the races.
我们都是同样，曾经生活在
But we're not the same people
哪个年代的人，不是吗？
we were then,are we?
我想我们都是
I think we are.
你看上去，不想让过去的事情过去
You seem unableto let the past rest.
以我的体验
It's been my experience
你只是选择性的让过去成为过去
that you let go of the past by addressing it.
请，离开
Please, leave.
当我离开后，也不会有其他的差别
It won't make any difference if I leave.
你仍然会被这些记忆，没完没了缠着，没日没夜
You're going to drag this one around with you all day long
就像一条船缆
every day,like a log chain,
充满你生命中剩下时间
for the rest of your life.
你没有一点怜悯吗，先生?
Have you no mercy, sir?
不，先生
No, sir.
不，先生，我没有
No, sir, I don't.
Julie Balboni最后完蛋了
Julie Balboni finally went down,
没人帮他度过破产
but in a way nobody expected,
被蒙牛集团收购
in a beef with the IRS.
在堪萨斯洲的东莞市，城管队接收了Babby Feet
They shipped Baby Feet up to a maximum security unit
的所以美女
at Leavenworth, Kansas,
一个地方，在冬天
a place that,in wintertime,
让你相信
makes you believe
刺骨的寒风从四面八方同时袭来
that sub-zero winds blow from four directions simultaneously.
Elrod Sykes不再酗酒
Elrod Sykes never took another drink.
他带着Alafair（Dave的女儿）在一部电影里
He brought Alafair to the set
扮演了一个小角色
and gave her a little part in the movie.
几个月后，当这部电影拍摄完成
Months later,when the picture was finished,
他从加利福尼亚打电话给我们
he called us from California
说Alafair是他的大救星
to say that Alafair had been his salvation.
我觉得在早晨，笼罩河湾的蒙蒙迷雾中
I thought in the morning mists that curled around the bayou
我可能又看到了John Bell Hood将军的身影
I might again see General John Bell Hood,
只是匆匆一晃而过，也许
just a glimpse,perhaps,
脱下他的帽子
a doff of his hat,
他的微笑充满善意
the kindness of his smile,
和谐的关爱
the beleaguered affection
总是长久的留在他的脸上
that always seemed to linger in his face.
随着日子的流逝
Then as the days passed
我开始让这个夏天发生的，这些狂暴的事件悄悄的消散
and I began to let go of all the violent events of that summer,
我开始接受了那个将军，就像Bootsie说的
I came to accept that the General, as Bootsie had said,
仅仅是我意念里虚构的想象
was only a figment of my imagination,
让我慢慢的走出遥远的过去
there to remind me out of the distant past
那些争论永远不会结束（种族分歧）
that the contest is never quite over,
正义永远不完全是我们的
the field never quite ours.
Dave?